http://www.wyomingbankers.com/?page=privacystatement

Privacy Statement - Wyoming Bankers Association
Search »
Print Page   |   Contact Us   |   Sign In   |   Register
HomeAbout
WBA CommitteesBoard of DirectorsMeet our PresidentPrivacy Statement
Education
Entire Education CalendarConventionConferencesWorkshopsOnline TrainingContinuing EducationCertification ProgramsGraduate Schools of Banking
EmploymentMembersBusiness PartnersLinks & Sites
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
Privacy Statement
The WBA website does not collect personal information about site users except and only when knowingly provided by users. Information regarding users of this site is used solely in the legitimate conduct of our business. Member information will not be used, collected, or retained by WBA unless there is a legitimate business purpose to do so. The collected information will only be used to help WBA manage this site. Such information will not be transferred to other parties unless otherwise noted at point of collection.  WBA website users should be aware when they voluntarily disclose personal information, information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties.  WBA may use software tools to gather information about site visitors’ browsing activity and the information may include date and time of visit, browser type, and how you got to our site.
Other information may be collected and retained during our business relationship with you, for example your e-mail address, we will retain the content of the mail, the address and our response to handle further questions you may have or as follow-up.
Our Website has links to a variety of state and federal agencies as well as private businesses and organizations. When you link to another site, you are no longer on the WBA site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us
Members Only
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't registered yet?
Education / Events
more
10/11/2020 » 10/16/2020Bank Technology Security School10/13/2020Customer Due Diligence Update10/13/2020How to Lead Successfully in a Complex, Uncertain Workplace - A Resilience Bootcamp10/13/2020Fundamentals of Interest Rate Swaps and Caps10/14/2020W9, W-8BEN and W-8BENE for Deposit Accounts
lEGISLATIVE nEWS
FIX DODD-FRANK!
Click the image to watch the video
Featured Members
Wyoming Bankers Association (WBA)
200 East 8th Ave., Suite 201
Cheyenne, Wyoming 82001
Phone:
1-307-638-5008
Fax:
1-307-638-5013
Email:
Office@WyomingBankers.com
Membership Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
